<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3 | Sylvain Chatel</title>
    <link>https://example.com/publication-type/3/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/publication-type/3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>3</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication-type/3/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>PELTA -- Shielding Multiparty-FHE against Malicious Adversaries</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/pelta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/pelta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Multiparty fully homomorphic encryption (MFHE) schemes enable multiple parties to efficiently compute functions on their sensitive data while retaining confidentiality. However, existing MFHE schemes guarantee data confidentiality and the correctness of the computation result only against honest-but-curious adversaries. In this work, we provide the first practical construction that enables the verification of MFHE operations in zero-knowledge, protecting MFHE from malicious adversaries. Our solution relies on a combination of lattice-based commitment schemes and proof systems which we adapt to support both modern FHE schemes and their implementation optimizations. We implement our construction in PELTA. Our experimental evaluation shows that PELTA is one to two orders of magnitude faster than existing techniques in the literature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest version of this paper can be found on &lt;a href=&#34;https://ia.cr/2023/642&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ePrint&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verifiable Encodings for Secure Homomorphic Analytics</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/veritas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/veritas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Homomorphic encryption, which enables the execution of arithmetic operations directly on ciphertexts, is a promising solution for protecting privacy of cloud-delegated computations on sensitive data. However, the correctness of the computation result is not ensured. We propose two error detection encodings and build authenticators that enable practical client-verification of cloud-based homomorphic computations under different trade-offs and without compromising on the features of the encryption algorithm. Our authenticators operate on top of trending ring learning with errors based fully homomorphic encryption schemes over the integers. We implement our solution in VERITAS, a ready-to-use system for verification of outsourced computations executed over encrypted data. We show that contrary to prior work VERITAS supports verification of any homomorphic operation and we demonstrate its practicality for various applications, such as ride-hailing, genomic-data analysis, encrypted search, and machine-learning training and inference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest version of this paper can be found on &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2207.14071&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ArXiv&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
